♪ ♪
Promo one, take one.
How's the hair? MAN 2: Perfect.
Women who make love on
airplanes, tomorrow on Galloway.
Promo two, take one.
Married women and their lesbian
lovers, tomorrow on Galloway.
Great. That stunk!
Promo two, take two.
Married women and
their lesbian lovers,
tomorrow on Galloway.
What do you think, Dan?
Perfect.
Promo three, take one.
Men who can't get enough,
tomorrow on Galloway.
And cut!
Okay, people, let's pull
cameras back to show positions.
Cut. That's it?
You were great, Nick.
That's better!
Where's that coffee?
Lisa Bateman.
I don't care what
Dan's upset about.
I'm not coming down to the set.
Tell him whatever you want.
No, wait.
Tell him, as his
executive producer,
I want him to get a haircut.
Yeah. Okay, bye.
And so it should be fun.
Nothing fancy.
Just the basic
three-guest setup.
But, uh, I don't
have to tell you
how this is done, do I?
You could probably
give me a few pointers.
Well, there's really nothing
to concern yourself with.
Thanks.
Leanne.
Wow.
Can't believe I
finally got you here.
You look great.
Thank you.
How long is it you two
have, uh, seen each other?
Three years?
Five. Is, uh,
everybody set?
I'm ready. Yeah?
Well, then you'll
excuse me then.
I have a few last minute
things to take care of.
So I'll, I'll give you ladies
some time to get acquainted.
Okay.
Hello, dear. Nice to see you.
Hello. Nice to see you again.
Uh... be kind.
In five, four, three...
Women in power.
From Cleopatra to Imelda Marcos,
it's long been an
issue for debate...
Brains versus breasts.
Do women deserve
prominent positions
or do they position
themselves to gain prominence?
That's the focus of this
edition of Dan Galloway.
My guests today are three
women, all personal friends of mine,
who exemplify women at the top.
First, Katherine Randolph.
Her nationally syndicated column
is the last word on
Beverly Hills style.
Next, Marla Cordante,
who made headlines prosecuting
the Atkinson murder trial,
and is now a judge
on the appellate court.
And finally, Leanne
Wilson, who for four years,
was my co-host
on A.M. Bakersfield.
She's given up the limelight
for a more fulfilling life,
and now owns Bakersfield's
first wedding consultancy firm.
Please, welcome all of them.
Katherine, as a woman
whose job it is to comment...
Dan, sorry, we got a
problem in the booth.
It'll just be a minute.
We need to get a
reading on all your mics.
So, if you could each just state
your name, then count to ten.
Katherine. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
Hold your places people.
We're gonna go again
just as soon as we
get audio cleared up.
Well, the problem is that women
have to walk a very fine line.
We want to retain our femininity
without being
viewed as seductive.
Yes.
She makes it all sound
good, but any man can tell you,
when a woman isn't
getting what she wants
in business or at home,
she gets it the
old-fashioned way.
Oh, you mean she earns it.
I can't believe you said that.
Believe it.
Yes?
Michelle Thomas to see you.
Send her in.
Michelle! Lisa!
Welcome to L.A.
Oh, it's been too long. Yeah.
Carr Dormitory. Overlooking
the Drama department.
Yeah, freshmen. Yeah.
Whoo! Look how far you've come.
Oh, boy, the years, huh?
What if someone actually
figures out how many years?
We'll just say they're lying.
I'm glad you're here.
We couldn't resist your offer.
Where's Mr. Matlock?
Call him "Ben." Okay.
He's people watching.
He'll be along.
This is my first chance
at substance and quality.
And I can't thank
either of you enough
for agreeing to
make an appearance.
Well, it sounds great.
Real Law, a show with
lawyers about real cases.
Mm-hmm. A real insight
into the legal system.
Lisa Bateman.
Vicious rumors or fact?
Judge Cordante has risen
to the top of her profession
in record time.
Here she is with
Governor Leon Grees.
Now, with Congressman
Robert Arnold.
And here with State Party
Chairman Edward Dorfman.
Would you not assume that she's
offering these gentlemen
more than professional opinions?
Now, what do you think?
What do you think?
No, it was just a
technical difficulty.
We had to start the show again.
Yeah, we'll postmortem
this later. Okay, bye.
He can't be that big a jerk.
Can and is.
You're not planning to use him
on Real Law, are you?
God forbid.
I didn't invent Dan Galloway.
He created himself.
With any luck,
this'll be my future.
He's gotta be acting.
Nobody's that big a jerk.
Excuse me.
Lisa Bateman.
I'm gonna let you work.
Okay, just a second.
We're having dinner, aren't we?
You bet. Ben, too. Oh, great.
I'll explain the show to
you then, and thanks again.
You are both going
to be wonderful!
Okay. Okay.
What is it?
Those were pictures
taken at various
political events.
You've used them out of context.
And I'm not going to
stay here any longer
and dignify this with an answer.
And, uh, now, a word
from our sponsor.
And we're in commercial.
Marla! Marla!
Marla! Marla! Marla!
Baby, you were great.
Your decision to
storm off... Brilliant.
You creep! You
made a fool out of me.
I made a personality out of you.
You're sick! And I'm an idiot
for ever appearing on your show.
- You loved it.
I'll invite you back.
You'll hear from my attorney.
30 seconds.
I've got 20 seconds.
What?
Are you one of the
guests on the next show?
How's that?
Are you one of the guys
who can't get enough?
Enough what?
Sex.
What, wha...?
What, what are
you talking about?
You know,
I just want to know how a
guy your age can sustain it.
How you come off
asking me a question
like that?! Hey, save
that for the show, Rupert.
Save that for the show.
My name's not Rupert!
And I'm not on any show.
What do you
think of that, jerk?!
Guy's a jerk.
That's Dan Galloway.
Dan Galloway's a jerk.
Five, four, three...
Jerk!
Welcome back.
Katherine. Leanne.
How do you answer to your
reputation as dragon ladies?
I mean, this is a classic case
where a man who is
opinionated, dominant,
uh, a perfectionist
is deemed a leader.
Whereas a woman
with exactly the same
characteristics is
labeled a "bitch."
Exactly.
That's why I chose to
leave the television business.
Leanne, didn't you
leave your job because
your contract wasn't renewed?
I mean, didn't your
sudden decision
to devote your
life to coordinating
napkins with
centerpieces come about
because your reputation
made it impossible
for you to get another
job in television?
My decision was based
on the fact that I was set up,
in the same way
by the same person
as I'm being set up now.
My dear, we're all being set up.
But I mean, what can you expect?
Let us not forget
that this is the man
who parachuted nude into
the Hollywood Bowl parking lot
just to get an
extra rating point.
Well, is that any worse
than ridiculing people
for not being invited
to some society party,
and then trashing those who were
for wearing the
same dress twice?
Careful, Katherine.
Move too fast, your face
might fall.
And we're in
commercial. Thank you.
That should be good
for another 41 share.
Piece of cake.
Well, Dan, you can put
that one in your scrapbook.
'Cause none of our stations
are gonna run that show.
Oh, sweetie.
You don't mean that.
It was tasteless, defamatory,
and left us wide
open for lawsuit.
It's controversy.
It's heat.
Public eats it up.
Look at the ratings.
It was crap.
Slanderous crap.
And I'm not gonna run it.
Mmm.
Poor Lisa.
So refined.
So... tasteful.
Much too good
for Dan, am I right?
I never said that.
Sweetie, it's
written all over you.
Let's not fight.
I, uh... I bought you a present.
Go ahead.
Open it.
What's the occasion?
Don't you get it?
I'm giving you the axe.
Sweetie...
guess who bought the
company last month.
The Vesten Corporation.
And guess who is the
Vesten Corporation.
Think hard, sweetie.
Vesten is an anagram for Steven.
Which is whose middle name?
Oh, my God.
And as the new president,
not only am I in
control, which, uh,
means of course that
today's show will air,
but you, my dear,
are out of a job.
I don't believe this.
Poor little Lisa's in shock.
But tastefully.
You're insane!
This is all a game to you!
You don't even deserve to live!
Temper, temper.
Oh, did I mention to you
that I need your offices cleaned
out by tomorrow morning?
There's some empty
boxes in the mailroom.
Say, why don't you ask?
Lisa?
Still here?
Why not?
You have nowhere to go.
I'm sorry.
You came all this
way for nothing.
No, the trip was fine.
But I want nothing
to do with this show...
This Real Law... if Dan
Galloway is gonna do it.
I don't think
Dan'll do the show.
It's not exactly his style.
Style.
When did being a
jerk become a style?
Hmm.
Well, at least we've
had some time together.
Yeah. Lisa Bateman? Yes?
I'm Lieutenant Burner
of the Los Angeles Police.
We have a warrant
for your arrest.
What?
You're being charged with
the murder of Dan Galloway.
You have the right
to remain silent.
If you give up that right,
anything you say or do can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
Don't say another word, Lisa.
Ben and I are
going to defend you.
I can't tell you how
much I appreciate this.
What are friends for?
Well, they got a pretty
good case against you.
You were in the building
at the time of the murder,
an eyewitness heard
you threaten him,
and your fingerprints are
all over the murder weapon.
Ben, the only time I saw
that axe was in his office.
And I left it there.
Well, who else could've
gotten hold of it?
Anyone.
Anyone who works in the studio.
Anyone who had a
pass to the building today.
The three women who were
on the show this afternoon...
They were all angry
enough to want to kill him.
Hmm.
Well, how can we see
a tape of that show?
You find anything? Not much...
Matches, the top of
a pen, all the typical
of what you'd find on
the floor of an office.
They tracing this?
According to the police,
that button wasn't found
on any of the clothing Joe was
wearing the day of the murder.
Not that that helps; it could
have dropped off anytime.
Well, yeah,
yeah, yeah, but...
doesn't a cleaning crew
come in here every night?
Sure, they do, but with the
way people clean nowadays,
we figure it could have
been here for months.
Yeah.
You mind if I hang on to this?
Well, with your
client's fingerprints
all over the murder weapon...
Yeah, you probably
won't be needing this.
I won't let it get away from me.
Was this machine unplugged
when the body was found?
Must have been.
We searched the room;
nobody changed anything.
Hmm. Huh.
Hmm.
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
I sure hope so.
I'm investigating
Mr. Galloway's murder.
I was home when it happened.
No, no, I'm not
investigating you.
When you finish using
one of these machines,
do you unplug it?
Unplug it?
No, it's like a TV set.
You just turn it off
when you're through.
Huh, so if one of these
machines is unplugged,
would you say someone
unplugged it on purpose?
Yeah.
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
Tape's still in the machine,
so we'll plug it in
and it should come up.
And what we'll see is whatever
Dan Galloway saw
when he unplugged it?
That's right.
Well, I'll be damned.
Yes, I stormed off
the set and, yes,
I was murderously
angry at Dan Galloway.
You can understand why.
Oh, oh, sure, sure.
Man was a jerk.
Yes.
But I did not kill him.
Now, I would like to discuss
this with you at length,
but I'm preparing a decision
that I have to
render this afternoon,
so I must ask you to excuse me.
It's lunchtime, so
why couldn't we...
I'm lunching in.
Perhaps we can talk
tomorrow. Call me.
Judge Cordante, would you say
that Dan Galloway
was the kind of person
who ever did anything
without a purpose?
Mr. Matlock,
I really am busy.
A-A-At the moment he was killed,
he was watching a tape of
the show that you appeared on.
Yes. Although he was dying,
he left, what I believe,
was a dying message.
He pulled the plug
from an editing machine
so the tape would
end on your face.
Me? Yes, your face
was on the screen
when Dan Galloway died.
Mr. Matlock, if this is
how you plan to build
a case against me,
I would suggest that you
look for another profession.
Now, really, I must
get back to work.
I'm not building anything, yet.
It would just seem to me,
that, as an officer of the court,
you'd be more cooperative.
All right.
Now, it's my understanding
that the murder happened
between 7:00 and 7:15.
And I know for a
fact that by then,
I was already having
dinner with a friend.
Now, I must insist that you go.
If you have any more questions,
call me in the morning. Okay.
But, uh, why,
why would a woman
of your stature,
a judge, agree to appear
on the Galloway show?
Well, um...
Well, I wanted to host
his new legal advice
show, Real Law.
Real Law.
No, I'm not going to give
up law for show business,
at least not permanently,
but, well, I did think
it would be interesting
and lucrative for awhile.
Yeah. Well, it hasn't
hurt Judge Wapner.
No, I guess not.
Of course, he actually
is in show business.
I should have called you, Phil.
Her Honor's lunching out today.
Don't worry, I'll pay you.
♪ ♪
Mr. Matlock, what
are you doing here?
I thought we'd finish our
conversation over lunch.
You're David Cabot.
That's right.
Your Honor,
you shouldn't be
seen with this man.
That's none of your business.
But he's all over the papers,
indicted for tax fraud,
SEC violations...
Indicted, not convicted.
And Judge Cordante
is free to be seen
with whomever she likes.
She can't feel that free.
Otherwise, she'd see
you out in the open,
not hiding under some fishpond.
I don't like what you're
insinuating, Mr. Matlock.
I'll say it right out loud.
Being seen with you could hurt
the judge's
reputation and career.
Mr. Matlock, I will answer
your questions right now.
You know what I want to know.
Who were you with at
the time of the murder?
She was with me.
You'll testify to that?
Of course.
Is that what you want?
No!
I mean, I was with David, but...
Please.
Your Honor, you're placing me
in a very awkward position.
I'll tell you what I'll do.
I'll keep this little
bit of information
in my hip pocket for a while.
Good luck to you.
Thank you.
I can't wish you luck.
I've read the charges
against you, and
I'll just wish you a miracle.
You saw Judge Cordante?
Yeah.
Maybe she's sowing
a few wild oats,
or getting a little
poison out of her system.
What are you talking about?
Well, pretty soon she may
be in another line of work.
But she does have an alibi.
But Dan Galloway
went to a lot of trouble
to name her as the
killer before he died.
Well, maybe he's trying
to tell us something else.
What?
We have nothing to go on.
No.
Not much.
I don't understand it.
Well, you knew him.
That was the style.
I'm sorry it worked
out this way.
Well, it's not your fault.
So, what happens to you now?
Well, with Dan dead,
the corporation's
asked me to stay on.
Oh. Oh, hello.
Oh, you're Miss Wilson.
Yes. Uh, Ben Matlock.
Oh, yes, you're
Lisa's attorney, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
I understand that you used
to work with, uh, Dan Galloway
and didn't, uh... You
didn't part as friends.
Well, Mr. Matlock,
that was five years ago.
Ancient history. Yeah.
But then he invited you
down here to do his show,
and humiliated you.
You'd think I'd know
better, wouldn't you?
Well, I'd be the first to admit
that Dan Galloway was a...
A jerk, yeah.
But I didn't kill him. Yeah.
Uh, what did you do, uh,
after the taping was finished?
All I really wanted
to do was get home.
So, I ran back to my motel.
I packed, checked out and
drove back to Bakersfield.
I see.
Thanks again, Lisa.
You've been great.
And good luck to you,
Mr. Matlock. Thank you.
What'd she want?
She wanted to know
about the possibility
of hosting Real Law.
Dan promised it to her.
It was gonna be
her big comeback.
His way of making
up for the past.
Well, that's interesting.
He promised the
same job to Marla.
What's even more interesting is
I set the host for the
show a month ago,
and Dan knew it.
Huh.
Three women who...
You know what I think?
All personal friends of mine...
I think that button's
got nothing to do with it.
Wait, wait.
Can you rewind
that part right there?
Yeah, can-can you...
Can you slow it down?
Stop it.
That's it.
It's the-the bracelet.
See?
Hey, look. Hmm?
$500 for a diary.
It's called an organizer, Ben.
Hmm.
It's made of ostrich. Oh.
Well, I wouldn't give
$500 for the whole ostrich.
Yes, may I help you?
I hope so.
We're trying to track
down this bracelet.
I'm sorry the
photograph is grainy,
but it's a still taken
from a videotape.
Do you recognize it?
Well, of course.
That's an Andrea
Claggett design.
Uh, Ben. Oh.
Do you know if this button
came from that bracelet?
Oh, no.
Andrea Claggett never
uses a button of this type.
Well, are-are you sure?
There are a lot of
buttons on that bracelet.
This button is brass.
Andrea Claggett uses
only precious metals.
Thanks. Uh-huh.
Where you going?
I don't know.
I might go over to
Katherine Randolph's.
You think... you
think Leanne did drive
straight to Bakersfield
after the taping?
I can sure try to
find out. Yeah.
I'll meet you back
in Jill's office?
About 3:00? 3:00.
So, anyway, after
the show was finished,
I raced back here to
re-write my column.
Do sit down.
Oh, thank you. Oh.
Hello?
She didn't!
Of course, you know, I had
something else ready to go,
but after what happened...
No, no, no, I'm still here.
In public?
So-so-so-so, you were
a little late?
9:00-ish.
They were fighting?
Of course, you know, I
did pop out for a bite to eat
around 7:00, but...
I don't believe it!
Uh, were you alone?
Yeah, Candy, could you
hold on for just one moment?
You know, let's not mince words.
I mean, Dan Galloway...
Whoever murdered
him did us a favor.
Well, you were awfully mad.
Throwing that vase
at him on the show.
Oh, my dear, Galloway and
I have been at it for years.
I mean, if what happened on
Tuesday was reason to kill him,
he would've been dead long ago.
No, no, listen...
No, there's no time like
the present, my darling.
I shall be there right away.
I'm so sorry.
I have to go.
Uh, oh.
Oh! Damn!
Oh. Oh.
Goodness. Mmm.
Oh.
Uh, no-no wonder.
No wonder. Look, look, look.
See? You're-you're
missing a button.
Oh, well, it's
always coming off.
Ah. Oh, look. Whoever
knows where it is now.
Now, look.
Oh. See?
Wh-where did that come from?
Well, it's yours,
isn't it yours?
No, no, no.
Mine's made of-of
hand-carved teak.
That's not it.
Okay.
I'll show you to the elevator.
Oh, uh, all right.
Thank you.
How nice.
Well, our girl, Kathy Randolph,
was having a little
quiet dinner alone
when, uh, Mr. Galloway
was done in.
So, she doesn't
have an alibi. Mmm.
Did you check out
Leanne's motel?
Yes, but the manager
was out with the flu
and no one else was authorized
to show me the
checkout registry.
We'll subpoena that.
We've seen the show three times.
Why again?
Well, I don't know.
That Galloway fella
never did anything
without a reason.
If he programmed
something in that machine
at his dying moments,
there's something in there
he wants somebody to see.
Oh, good, we're ready.
Now, if the tape
was in that machine,
he was sitting about,
oh, I'd guess, right here.
And then someone
came through the door.
Would be somebody
he knew, wasn't afraid of.
'Cause you don't turn
your back on the enemy.
So, he was facing this
way when he was hit.
The killer raised the ax.
You be the killer.
Okay. And now he...
She. She, yeah, she...
she hit him.
And he fell.
Police outline.
See? Okay, now,
the killer thought he was dead.
So, he...
She split, see?
And that's when he left a clue.
He...
got up and he...
programmed the keyboard.
And then he pulled the plug.
Now, can you...
Now, can you run the tape,
and stop it where he
programmed it to stop.
Sure.
Kyle, next.
I'll be dogged.
Of course, that's it.
That's it.
But you gotta get down here.
You gotta get down on the floor.
Yeah, now.
We've been looking
at this all wrong.
See, the picture has
nothing to do with it.
It's the counter.
But...
the counter says
three, three, seven.
How are you gonna prove it?
Leanne did it and
we will prove it.
We've still got the button.
Of course, it didn't
come off her bracelet.
And it doesn't match
anything else she was wearing.
And we've seen the
entire show three times.
Now, wait a minute.
We haven't seen the entire show.
They stop the show
and then restart.
At least some of that would've
been caught on the master.
But, uh, mmm, the stop and start
would've been edited from
the copies that you saw.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, that's good, you got it.
Now, can you rewind
that and play it back for us?
Sure.
Stop.
There she is. See?
Wearing a jacket.
Now, can you... can
you put up the other tape?
You bet.
And when you come to a
place with Leanne stop it.
Judge on the appellate court.
- And finally, Leanne Wilson...
- Yeah. Yeah.
Now there she isn't
wearing a jacket.
See?
But it doesn't help us.
The buttons on that jacket still
don't match the one we have.
We still don't have anything.
Oh, yes, we do.
Lisa, Leanne Wilson
returning your call, line two.
Leanne, hi.
Look, the reason I'm calling
is the host that we set for
Real Law isn't working out.
I was wondering if
you would come in
and test for a replacement.
Tomorrow at 10:00.
Good.
Look, wear that red suit that
you wore on the Galloway show,
you look great in it.
No, don't worry.
We'll correct the sound
problem with the jacket.
Okay, great.
Bye-bye.
You're gonna have a good time.
Just relax and be yourself.
Sure, I'm looking forward.
Oh, it'll be fine, everything's
very laid back here.
Leanne, I think you
know Ben Matlock.
Oh. He's agreed to
play guest for us today.
Oh, hello, Mr...
Oh, oh! Oh, oh, I'm so...
Oh, I'm sorry!
Oh, oh, look, now. It's okay.
How awful, I got coffee...
No, it's all right. Oh...
Oh, I'm just making it worse.
No, no, it's all right.
Really, I'm fine.
Did it burn you? No, no.
Oh, I'm just so sorry.
You know, I don't think
it's gonna show on camera
but I insist that you
let wardrobe clean it.
So, do you want to
take it off, Leanne?
That's really nice
of you, thank you.
Sorry, oh, I just. It's okay.
You sit down here on the left
and Ben, if you have
a seat on the right.
Okay. Okay.
Now, this is just a
rehearsal... Yeah.
So I want you to
have fun with it.
Fun. All right.
That's it, we'll have fun.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
And I... You sure
it didn't burn you?
I'm fine, it's fine,
it's really fine.
Now, let's see.
You used to work
with Dan Galloway.
Yes, we were talk show
co-hosts in Bakersfield.
Yeah, and now, how
long ago was that?
Five years.
But he decided he wanted more
and despite the fact that
you were both very successful,
you were not part of his plans.
Mr. Matlock, it's not unusual
for teams in this
business to split up.
It happens all the time.
I guess it does,
I guess it does.
But considering the fact
that you were both
so equally successful,
it just seems
rather odd, I mean,
uh, one goes on
to fame and fortune
and the other is left behind.
Objection!
I fail to see the relevance.
Uh, Your Honor,
the history between this
witness and the deceased
is critical to the foundation
of the rest of my questioning.
I'll overrule for now.
Continue.
Thank you.
Uh, in fact,
uh, he actually
undermined you, didn't he?
He portrayed you
as temperamental
and with much less
talent than, than he had
and then he walked out on
you and while his career soared,
uh, you were reduced to making
ends meet by planning weddings.
Isn't that true?
I'm very proud of what I do.
I'm very sure you are.
I'm very sure you are
but, uh, a few weeks ago,
the phone rang and
it was Dan Galloway
offering you a spot on his show
and you dropped everything
and ran right down here.
Why?
What did he say to you?
He told me I'd be the perfect
guest on a show he was planning.
After five years of silence
and all he did to you?
Isn't it true that you
agreed to be on his show
because he promised to
give you the position of host
on a new talk show?
He did mention that.
Did he also mention
that the position of host
had already been set
and that it had been offered
to several other women?
No.
Yeah.
I have a signed
affidavit right here
from Judge Marla Cordante...
which says that
he offered her
that same position.
Dan Galloway
was a terrible man.
He was a world-class jerk.
He liked to play games
with people's lives.
Any number would've
wanted him dead,
but only one
could've killed him.
And unfortunately
for him or her,
he played one last
game just before he died.
He left a clue.
Bailiff?
When Judge Cordante's
picture appeared on the monitor
we thought he
was trying to tell us
that she had killed him
but then we have to
remember he was dying.
He was on the floor.
He was looking at the
monitor upside down.
And when he pulled that plug,
this digital counter
stopped at 337.
But if you look
at it upside down,
the way he did,
it spells "L-E-E."
You see that, Leanne?
As you said, Dan was a jerk.
All this means is that he
was trying to set me up again.
And besides, at the
time he was killed,
I was already
back in Bakersfield.
No.
Thank you.
You checked out
of the motel at 6:00.
But you left your car
in the motel garage
until almost 8:00.
That places you in Los Angeles
well within the
time of the murder.
As a matter of fact, it places
you at the scene of the crime,
and before you
say I have no proof,
I'm gonna take a shot at it.
This button was found on
the floor of the editing room
where Dan Galloway was killed.
I guess the police
thought it wasn't important
and I didn't at first.
But you know, they
vacuum that room every night
and just four days
before the murder,
that room was recarpeted.
The old carpet was thrown away.
Somebody who owns this button
has to be involved
in this whole thing.
Somebody. Objection!
Your Honor, I don't know
how they try cases in Atlanta,
but this is the time for
questioning the witness,
not for argument,
so... Your Honor,
four days before the murder,
the room was recarpeted.
The old carpeting and
everything that was on it
was torn up and thrown away.
This button is evidence.
Objection overruled.
Continue, Mr. Matlock.
Thank you.
But it doesn't seem
to belong to anybody.
It doesn't seem to
come off anything.
have done anything.
When you came down,
uh, to do the taping,
you were wearing a jacket
but then when you actually
did the taping, you
weren't wearing the jacket.
Some sort of sound problem.
I wore my red jacket.
It doesn't have
any brass buttons,
Mr. Matlock.
Not on the outside.
But all double-breasted coats
have buttons on the inside
to make sure they hang right.
Now, your jacket was made by...
Francesca di Giovanni?
Right? Yes.
Bailiff?
Now, this is a rack of
Miss Giovanni's jackets.
And as you can see,
the inside buttons are brass.
See?
Brass.
All brass.
Just like this button that
was found on the floor
by Dan Galloway's body.
Now, you recognize
this jacket, don't you?
It's yours, isn't it?
I remember spilling coffee
on the sleeve the other day.
But your inside button doesn't
match the brass buttons.
Your inside button
is white, isn't it?
I lost the original
button months ago.
I don't think so.
I think you lost this button
when you raised the
axe to kill Dan Galloway.
No.
I distinctly remember I
lost the button last October.
At a country club wedding
reception that I planned.
Then why did you wait
till the day after Dan
Galloway was killed
to take your coat
to the Forest
Drycleaners in Bakersfield
and have them
replace this button?
The cleaner's mark
is still inside the jacket.
And we talked to the management.
Why did you wait
till the day after Dan
Galloway was killed
to replace this button?
Can you answer that?
Would you like to
retain an attorney?
Yes.
That's wise.
No further questions.
We find the defendant,
Lisa Bateman, not guilty.
Court is adjourned.
Thank you!
And how you did
it, I don't know.
Well, it wasn't easy.
Can I take you to dinner?
Oh, well, thanks
but I guess I'm,
I guess I'm pretty
much a home boy.
A home boy?
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna go
home, Atlanta, get a bite to eat,
maybe a hot dog all the way,
put on my green striped
pajamas, go to bed.
Okay.
How about you?
Well, aside from the hot dog
and the green striped pajamas,
I guess I'm pretty
much a home girl.
www.tvsubtitles.net